{"data":[{"question":"Tom's brother raises a lot of ___ in his backyard.","a":"sheepes","b":"sheeps","c":"sheepen","d":"sheep","answer":"4","explain":"- Singular and plural of \"Sheep\" is \" Sheep\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"It won't make much ___ whether those people agree or not.","a":"difference","b":"trouble","c":"differences","d":"troubles","answer":"1","explain":"- Make a\/the difference:\t to have an important effect or influence on something or someone\n\n- Diffenence can be use as coutable and uncountable noun\n\n- Much + uncountable noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Where is your father? \"At _________ .\"","a":"Mr. Green","b":"Mr. Green's","c":"the Mr. Green","d":"the Mr. Green's","answer":"2","explain":"\n- At Mr Green's = At Mr Green's house","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Marilyn and Jane are ___.","a":"my father and mother's friends","b":"my father and mother friends","c":"friends of mine father and mother","d":"my father's and mother's friends","answer":"1","explain":"- My father and mother's friends:  friends of both my father and my mother\n\n- My father's and mother's friends: friends of my father and\/or of my mother\n\n- Mine= my father","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The woman pianist played several ___ for the guests.","a":"piece of music","b":"musics","c":"pieces of music","d":"music","answer":"3","explain":"- Structure: Piece of something\n\n- Piece: countable noun=> plural: add \"s\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"___ not going to question everybody in the room.","a":"The policeman are","b":"The police is","c":"The police are","d":"The policemen is","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The police: the official organization whose job is to catch criminals and make sure that people obey the law \n- The police is plural ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"You mustn't lose ___ even when the rain washes away your plants.","a":"hearts","b":"heart","c":"your hearts","d":"the hearts","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Lose heart: Lose confidence and courage","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Food and ___ are daily necessities of the people.","a":"clothes","b":"cloth","c":"cloths","d":"clothing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Clothing: the clothes that people wear \n- Cloth: material used for making things such as clothes","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Does your friend have enough ___ to lift these weights?","a":"force","b":"power","c":"strength","d":"energy","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Strength: agree with \"lift these weight\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"She says she has got ___  in her shoulders.","a":"harm","b":"hurts","c":"suffering","d":"pains","answer":"4","explain":"- Pain (the feeling you have when part of your body hurts) is both countable and uncountable noun\n\n- Pain: conform with \"her shoulders\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}